Guide to the F. Jay Haynes Papers1870-1922bulk 1885-1916
Montana State University Library, Archives and Special Collections, Manuscript Collections
- Photography Business Records, 2
  - Photo Orders, 3
    - Photo orders, 1887 October 25-31 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Photo orders, 1887 November 1-7 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Photo orders, 1887 November 8-14 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Photo orders, 1887 November 15-21 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Photo orders, 1887 November 22-30 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Photo orders, 1889 July-August, December 1-14 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Photo orders, 1889 December 15-31 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Photo orders, 1890 January (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Photo orders, 1890 February (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Photo orders, circa 1889 December-1890 February (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Catalogue orders, 1889 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Photo orders, 1891-1905 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Catalogue orders, circa 1890s (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Business Correspondence, 4
    - Business correspondence, 1876-1881 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Business correspondence, 1883 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Mail registry receipts, 1883 (Box 8, Folder 2A)
    - Business correspondence, 1884 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Business correspondence, 1885 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - NPRR rail lease contract, 1885 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Business correspondence, 1886 September-December (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Business correspondence, 1887 January-March (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Business correspondence, 1887 April (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Business correspondence, 1887 May (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Business correspondence, 1887 June (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Business correspondence, 1887 July (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Business correspondence, 1887 August (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Business correspondence, 1887 September (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Business correspondence, 1887 October-December (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Business correspondence, 1889 January-November (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Business correspondence, 1889 December (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Receipts, etc., 1889 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Yellowstone Park Association hotel sales agreement, 1889 September 15 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Business correspondence, 1890-1891 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Undated notes, circa 1890 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Undated clippings, circa 1887-1891 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Business correspondence, 1890 January-June (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Minnesota National Guard Regiment honorary membership; Société Scientifique Européenne correspondence, See also 2:1., 1892 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Business correspondence, 1892-1893 June (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Business correspondence, 1893 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Business correspondence, 1894 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Yellowstone Park Association hotel sales agreement, 1894 May 19 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Business correspondence, 1895 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Freight bills, 1895 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Yellowstone Park Association hotel sales agreement, 1895 March 18 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Business correspondence, 1896 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Freight bills, 1896 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Business correspondence, 1897 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Business correspondence, 1898 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Business correspondence, 1899 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Business correspondence, 1900 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Business correspondence, 1901 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Business correspondence, 1902 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Business correspondence, 1903 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Business correspondence, 1904 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Business correspondence, 1905 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Business correspondence, 1907 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Business receipts, 1907 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Business correspondence, 1908 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Business correspondence, 1909 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Business correspondence, 1910 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Business correspondence, See also Collection 1504 43:11, 1911 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Business correspondence, 1912 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - List of Alaskan negative numbers, undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - 1912-13 Catalogue (Numerical) (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Business correspondence, Louis Glaser Gropische Kunstanstalt, 1913 January-1914 January (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Business correspondence, 1913 February-April (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Business correspondence, 1913 June-July (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Business correspondence, 1913 August-November (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Park business report, 1913 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Business correspondence, 1914 January-March (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Business correspondence, 1914 May-December (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - YNP photo concession correspondence, 1914 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - YNP lease agreements, 1914 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Data relative to the application of F. Jay Haynes for renewal of photographic concession in Yellowstone National Park, 1914 April 8 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Park business financial statement, 1914 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Park business financial statement, 1915 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Business correspondence, 1915-1917 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Business correspondence, 1920 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Transportation passes, See also 17:32, 1879-1915 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Cheque and Stub Registers, 5
    - Studio account? (6500-6599), 1894 April 5-May 10 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Studio account? (6600-6699), 1894 May 10-June 9 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Studio account? (6800-6899), 1894 July 24-September 1 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Studio account? (6900-6999), 1894 September 1-October 10 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Studio account? (7200-7299), 1894 December 29-1895 February 7 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Studio account?, St. Paul, 1905 November 15-1906 April 2 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Studio account?, St. Paul, 1906 April 6-December 18 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Park account, Gardiner, 1906 June 12-October 9 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Personal account? Passbook, Gardiner, 1906 June-September (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Studio account?, St. Paul?, 1907 November 23-1908 March 27 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Studio account?, St. Paul?, 1908 March 28-August 28 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Studio account?, St. Paul?, 1908-August 29-December 17 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Park account?, Gardiner?, 1906 October 12-27 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Personal account?, Fargo, 1879 May 29-[1880] March 2 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Personal account?, Fargo, 1880 April 9-1881 July 5 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Personal account?, Fargo, 1881 July 7-1882 June 26 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Personal account?, St. Paul, See also 1:13, 1905 November 14-1906 April 2 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - 1879 (Box 11, Folder 1-2)
    - 1880 (Box 11, Folder 3-4)
    - 1881 (Box 11, Folder 5-7)
    - 1882 (Box 11, Folder 8-10)
    - 1878-1882 (Box 11, Folder 11-14)
    - 1893 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - 1895 (Box 11, Folder 16-17)
    - 1896 (Box 11, Folder 18-20)
    - 1897 (Box 11, Folder 21-22)
    - 1898 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - 1899 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Haynes Studio Palace Car, 6
    - Studio Car floor plan (blueline drawing) Includes photonegative, 1885 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Narrative reports, 1886 November-1887 May (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Narrative reports, 1887 June-November (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Narrative reports, 1898 July-August (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Narrative reports, 1899, 1904 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Narrative reports, 1889 August-December (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Narrative reports, 1890 January-May (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Narrative reports, See also Collection 1501 bk.9, 1890 Jun, December, 1891 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Car log, 1890 June 11-1891 January 29 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Waybills (weekly negative register), 1-10, 1895 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Waybills (weekly negative register), 11-20, 1895 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Waybills (weekly negative register), 21-32, 1895 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Waybills (weekly negative register), 1-10, 1896 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Waybills (weekly negative register), 11-19, 1896 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Waybills (weekly negative register), 20-27, 1896 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Waybills (weekly negative register), 28-33, 1896 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Waybills (weekly negative register), undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Car operation contract, 1901 December 8 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Car business forms (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Business licenses (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Advertising bills, 1886, 1888 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Cash book, 1888 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Expenses, 1888 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - NPRR bills, 1890 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - NPRR bills, 1891 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - NPRR bills, 1892 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Bills payable, 1892 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Cash report, 1892 May 30-June 25 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Cash report, 1892 June 27-July 30 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Cash report, 1892 August 8-September 3 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Cash report, 1892 September 15-24 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - NPRR bills, 1893 January-July (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - NPRR bills, 1893 August-December (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Weekly reports, 1893 February 26-April 29 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Weekly reports, 1893 April 30-June 24 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Weekly reports, 1893 June 25-September 30 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Weekly reports, 1893 October 1-November 25 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Weekly reports, 1895 July 20, August 3 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Daily reports, 1896 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Weekly reports, 1896 April 25-July 27 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Weekly reports, 1896 July 4-August 29 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Weekly reports, 1896 September 5-October 31 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Weekly reports, 1896 November 7-December 12 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Weekly reports, 1898 April 16 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Daily reports, 1897, 1900 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Weekly reports, 1899 June 3 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Weekly reports, 1901 February 2 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Weekly reports, 1902 August-November (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Weekly reports, 1904 March 26 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Yellowstone National Park Photography Business, 7
    - Ground lease, 1884 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Tour party photo order lists, 1887 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Bills and statements, 1888 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - [YPA sales] commission on views [i.e. pictures sold], 1888 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Business correspondence, 1891 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - YPA accounts, 1891 June-August (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - YPA accounts, 1891 September-October (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Daily sales tallies (probably Mammoth), 1891 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Photo orders, 1892 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - YPA accounts, 1892 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Wylie Permanent Campground Company, 8
    - YPA accounts, 1893 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Park Studio sales tabulation and statement to Secretary of the Interior, 1893 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Mammoth ground lease renewal, 1894 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1895 March-December (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Upper Basin property contract, 1896 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Business correspondence, 1896 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Bills and accounts, 1896 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Shipping receipts, 1896 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Mounted Boudoir in Park [photo sales tally], 1896 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Business correspondence, See also Collection 1504 59:5, 1897 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Boudoirs for 1897 [YNP photo sales tally] (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - YPA bills, 1897 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Photo business in Yellowstone Park [statement], 1897 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Hotel sales proposal and agreement, 1897 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Business correspondence, 1898 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Composite photo/drawing of Madison Junction (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Park view record [photo sales tally], 1898 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Business correspondence, 1899 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Business correspondence, 1900 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - YPA accounts, 1901 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Business correspondence, 1902 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - YPA hotel sales contract, 1902 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Business correspondence, 1903 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Picture sales in Yellowstone Park, Season 1903 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Price schedule and slide list, 1904 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Supply orders, 1904 January-April (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Business correspondence, 1904 June 1-15 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Business correspondence, 1904 June 16-30 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - YPA accounts, 1904 June 24 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Billed-goods receipts, 1904 June (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Business correspondence, 1904 July 1-15 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Lease contracts, 1904-1913 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Billed-goods receipts, 1904 July (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Business correspondence, 1904 August 1-15 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Business correspondence, 1904 August 16-31 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Billed-goods receipts, 1904 August (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Business correspondence, 1904 September (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Billed-goods receipts, 1904 September (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Business correspondence, 1904 October-November (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Business correspondence, 1905 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Business correspondence, 1906 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Business correspondence, 1907-1910 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Park business statement, 1910 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Business correspondence, 1911 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - JEH Upper Basin subsistence account, 1911 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Petty cash receipts, 1912 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Business correspondence, 1912-1913 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Park order due bills, 1913 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Upper Basin Studio stock receipts, 1913 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - YNP freight shipments, 1913 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Billed-goods accounts, 1913 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Petty cash receipts, 1913 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - FJH subsistence account with W.A. Hall Co., 1913 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Business correspondence, See also 9:22-26, 1915 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Printed rate schedules, 1894, 1914 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Park photo orders, 1890 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Park photo orders, 1890 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Park photo orders, 1896 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Park photo orders, 1904 June-August (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Printing orders, 1904 September-October (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Printing orders, 1904 November (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Printing orders, 1904 December (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Park photo orders, 1908 June-September (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Park photo orders, 1912 June-August 7 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Park photo orders, 1912 August 8-September (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Share purchase contract, 1909 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1911-1916 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1917 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence regarding [WPCC] notes and stock, between A.L. Smith and FJH. Transcripts supplied by FJH to his lawyer., 1910-1915 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1918 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Weekly summary reports, 1911-1912 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Weekly summary reports, 1913-1915 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Misc. financial data, 1916 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Deed for stock sale to A.W. Miles, 1916 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Statement showing gross earnings, expenses, depreciation, profit, dividends and surplus, 1909-1916 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Acmegraph/Haynes postcard comparisons, 1912 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Yellowstone Park Stage-Business Records, 3
  A printed listing of individual folders in boxes 17-25 and flatfile is located in the reading room of Special Collections.
  - Yellowstone Park Stage Company (National Park Line), 1
    - Yellowstone Park Stage Company (Wakefield & Haynes); George Wakefield bills, 1885-1886, 1888-1898 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Monida and Yellowstone Stage Company, 2
    - Concession correpondence, 1897 December-1989 May (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - MY concession lease, 1898 May 28 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Description of route of [MY] stage line: Fountain Hotel to Monida (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1898 June-November (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Lease sites plat map, 1898 November 24 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1899 April-December (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Building sites lease, 1899 December 19 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Incorporation papers, 1900-1903 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1900 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, transportation passes, 1901 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Exchanged tickets, 1901 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Pocket notebook giving rates, 1901 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, transportation passes, 1902 May-October (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Finances and payroll, 1902 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1903 January-February (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, Henry W. Child to FJH, 1903 February 25 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, transportation passes, 1903 April-December (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Finances, 1903 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Yellowstone Park as an attraction to the Oregon Short Line R.R. and connections, 1903 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Freight received by rail at Cinnabar and Gardiner ..., 1903 September (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Concession sites leases 1903-1907 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Exchanged tickets, 1903 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, transportation passes, 1904 January-September (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Park rates and agreements; correspondence and minutes from a meeting in Chicago, 1904, 1903 December 15 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Certificate of amendments to articles of incorporation, 1904 March (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Inventories and auditor's statement, 1904 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence, 1905 January-June (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, 1905 July-November (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Statement of W.W. Humphrey account, 1899-1905 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Finances and auditor's statements, 1905 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Transportation passes, 1905 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence, 1906 January-April (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1906 May-June (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1906 August-September (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Letter to [Robert] Duff, circa 1906 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Finances, 1906 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Yellowstone National Park [rates] Meeting, 1906 Jan 16 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Monida Office cash account (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1907 January-September (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Finances; transportation passes, 1906-1907 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Tourists to Yellowstone Park during the month of June 1907, 1908 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1908 February-October (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Finances, 1908 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Advantages to travel through Yellowstone Park from the western entrance by having the hotel located at the junction of Gibbon and Firehole Rivers ...; "How to improve the Service in Yellowstone Park" (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1909 January-March (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1909 April (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1909 May-July (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 1909 August-September (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Covell, Earl D. "Report on location and feasibility of construction of a proposed road from Six Mile Post to Yellowstone, Mon.", 1909 September (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, 1909 October-December (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Finances, 1909 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - "Proposed [OSLRR] depot at Yellowstone," tracing blueline from 1907 draft and revised blueline, 1909 March (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, 1910 June-August (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, 1910 September-December (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Finances, 1910 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Tables of comparative travel statistics, 1899-1911 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Transportation in the Yellowstone National Park, corrected copy, 1911 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1911 March, June-September, November (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Finances, 1911 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Printed matter proofs (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Horse record, 1911 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Statistical summaries, 1899-1911 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Bookings, 1912 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1912 February-May (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, Tower Falls relay station, 1912 June (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Tower Falls relay station site and stable plans, see also Collection 1504 59:55, 1912 June (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Tour arrangements for W.I. Washburn, 1912 July-September (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1912 July-December (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Notes on railroad line to West Yellowstone, Mont. (probably written by or for MY lawyer James R. Hickey) (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Park travel statistics, 1912 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - YNP lease documents (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - OSLRR sales statement for 1911 Jan-Jun, 1912 January 10 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - OSLRR sales statement for 1911 Jul, 1912 May 10 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - OSLRR sales statement for 1911 Aug-Dec, 1912 June 10 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Financial reports, 1912 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Horse record, 1912 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Disbursement tallies [expenses], 1912 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Annual reports, 1912 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Payroll, 1912 June (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Misc. financial notes and receipts (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Bookings, 1913 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - OSLRR sales statement for 1912, 1913 April 24 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1913 January-April (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1913 May (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1913 June (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1913 July (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1913 August 1-22 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1913 August 26-30 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1913 September (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1913 October-December (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Telegram cipher, 1913 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Investigation of charges against the MY, 1913 June 14 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Recapitulation [of ticket income reporting] 1908-1912 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Bills for legal costs (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Desk and vault seals, 1913 July (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - "Old Faithful Inn, designed by F. Jay Haynes," blueline front elevation (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Party bookings calendar, 1913 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Memo of Park travel, 1911; party-ticket exchanges (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - OSLRR sales statement for 1913 Jan-Jun (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - OSLRR sales statement for 1913 Jul (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - OSLRR sales statement for 1913 Aug (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - OSLRR sales statement for 1913 Sep-Dec (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Income tax return, 1914 January 20 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Balance sheet and financial report, 1913 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Annual report, 1913 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Payroll items, 1913 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Advertising copy (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Misc. finance items, 1913 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Montana and Yellowstone Park Transfer Company, 3
    - Montana & Yellowstone Transfer Company incorporation, 1913 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - YW lease of Montana & Yellowstone Park Transfer Co. property, 1914 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Yellowstone-Western Stage Company, 4
    - Yellowstone-Western Stage Company corporation notices, 1913 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Bunkhouse drawings (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Bookings, 1914 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1914 January-July (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1914 August-December (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Union Pacific ticket agents' tour thank-you letters, 1914 (Box 21, Folder 14-16)
    - YW logographs (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Copies of printing on hand [YW form samples], 1914 (Box 21, Folder 18)